Tsuda, what's this I hear
about you buying a romance-bot?
Boss, I—
Miss Tsuda, tell me you're
not that kind of criminal!
Wait, guys—!
It's all right, master.
You can stay with me forever and ever.
NOOOOOOO!
Just... a dream...
Look how cozily she's sleeping.
Wait... but robots don't sleep.
Is she broken?!
Maybe her battery ran dry?
She has been up and
running since she got here.
There, that should do it.
Wait, where's her power button?
Hmm. Maybe on her back?
Nope...
Maybe in front?
Just a mole.
Oh my god, l am being
such a pervert right now!
Still, I can't leave her like this.
What's that?
A QR code!
Maybe I can learn something.
Thank you for your purchase!
This video will serve as your user
manual for your Nadeshiko sex android!
Let's start with booting her up!
Do I even need to boot her back up?
I don't want to get rid of her,
but maybe I should leave her as she is.
Ah, that's right!
I forgot I ordered this!
Okay!
To activate the unit,
give it a French kiss!
Gently press the switch
inside the unit's mouth!
Where is it? Where's the switch?
Master?
You're awake!
You wouldn't wake up so
I was sure you were broken!
What a relief!
I completely forgot to recharge my battery.
It's okay. I wasn't
thinking about it, either.
But first, come...
Um, master? What is this?
All I had that fit you was a schoolgirl
uniform, so I bought you this!
It has more of a cosplay
yibe than I expected, though...
That looks great on you!
You're adorable, Nadeshiko!
Did you just call me by my name?!
You did! You've never done that before!
I'm so happy!
Please, I want you to keep
addressing me like that more and more!
Oh. Oh, no...
She's so cute...
From now on, while you're sleeping,
I'll go into sleep mode as well, master!
S-Sure...
You can awake me from sleep mode
the same way you rebooted, me!
Huh?
The same as rebooting?!
It is a functional limitation
of master registration.
AUTHENTIFICATION
If you were registered, you could reuse
me from sleep mode via voice command.
NADESHIKO!
So you can complete master registration,
or manually wake me every morning.
Brought to you by ToonsHub
Which do you prefer, master?
I can't do eitherrrr!